We’re good, sir. Thank you very much.
We’re good too. You’re all in such a busy schedule.
Yes, yes. The series are going really well.
There’s a new song here.
ATV's two big hits. Yes.
And we have a singer saying “Enough.”
Exactly. I said "Enough." Welcome.
Yes Özge, let’s start with you.
Welcome. After 6 seasons, we finally have you sitting here. We've been working for 6 seasons—how nice.
We’re very busy, but 10 minutes... I know, I know.
Welcome, Bala Hatun. Thank you. Yes.
So, it’s going intensely, huh?
Of course, with working 6 days a week, I joined you on my day off today.
Thank you. Yes. And it’s your first series.
While studying, I even have one and a half terms left.
Well, when this opportunity came up, I found myself on this journey for 6 years.
How was it being in the lead role in your first series? It takes effort too.
But you know, you don’t start in the lead role right away.